I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you
For you to be
What is it?
There's a gap.
I'm about to pop.
I can't take it anymore.
I can't hold it.
Oh!
Oh! Oh! What?
Huh! What's this?
What is it?
I'm so nervous.
What is it? What is it?
What?
One for 100,000 rounds of premium goat meat for six.
Yes!
I got goat meat!
That's good.
Yay!
Goat meat?
I didn't get any tusks.
Today?
You want some?
Yay! Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Thanks to everyone spreading the love and watching so much,
We were able to support 10 million times,
And we got goat meat.
Thank you very much.
We will eat it deliciously.
We will eat it.
We will deliver it,
Please allow me to meet the members.
Yay.
Thank you very much.
See you soon.
Yes! What a day! The day we've been looking forward to for a long, long time is here!
Yay!
Yes, today is the day that our favorite live-erit super-version of the song has been viewed more than 10 million times,
What a surprise! We're here to eat some high quality yakiniku (barbecued meat)!
Oh no!
I love yakiniku!
This is what we've all been waiting for today.
When is it coming? They were asking when.
When? When? We've been asking.
He's here.
I'm so happy. It smelled so good.
That's why I ate less breakfast today.
I only ate one rice ball.
I'm here for real.
I'm here for Mr. Darko.
Here are the steps.
Mr. Kuroda.
This is Yakiniku Croda-san.
It's so beautiful.
Lots of places to eat.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm going to go now.
Kroda.
I'm going to eat.
It's amazing.
It smells so good.
More than green onions.
More than leeks.
You were on the menu twice recently.
You actually glanced at it.
I actually glanced at the menu,
Nana saw someone looking at the Instagram yesterday.
I was glancing at it.
It's not mushrooms.
What's ahi in ahi jus?
It's like the fangs of an ahi tuna.
Yuri said.
My favorite.
Thank you very much.
It's lotus root.
Chinese cabbage, vegetables too, lotus root and okra.
Is that Mr. Service?
It's delicious.
Thank you very much.
They're sorting it out.
She's a nice lady.
She's very sissy.
I feel like a big sister.
Thank you.
Congratulations.
Okay. - Okay.
OK.
Bon appétit!Bon appétit!
Thank you all!
Thanks to all of you, we had delicious meat!
Let's eat this and keep up the good work!
I'll do my best!
Bon appétit!
Delicious!
The meat is delicious
So good!
Crunchy
Delicious
Delicious.
I'm so hungry.
I'm not eating anything today.
Oh, my God.
I can't eat a single bite.
I ate this morning.
I had yogurt.
I had it at 6:00 a.m.
Okay, bye.
Julia, do you get up early in the morning?
Early. She makes the most of her mornings.
She's laid-back.
That's a great time.
What do you do in the morning?
I wake up, put on my makeup,
Check my hair color,
And clean up,
I'm ready to work.
Really?
I had a Build-A-Dose.
It's delicious.
It's amazing.
Oh, man.
Beef bowl is served.
Wow.
I love rice bowls.
Wow, that's great.
It's amazing.
It's absolutely delicious.
Kanami, it's a pork cutlet.
Yay.
It's a pork cutlet.
It's a pork cutlet!
Wow.
Tankatsu.
Delicious.
Wow.
How many times? Tankatsu.
How many times?
How many times? Like 10?
That's great.
First, you grill it, put some green onion revision on it, and try to eat it.
Wow! It sounds really good.
It's a good one with less baking time, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
Right away.
Is that what you call a good one?
Thank you.
Have a good day.
That's great.
Have a good night.
I think it's gonna burn really fast.
Really?
Really.
Oh, my God!
Is it coming?
It's coming, it's coming.
Oh, but I'm not good at this. I'm impatient.
It's okay. I can be impatient today.
But..,
I'm impatient, but I did it.
It's amazing.
It looks delicious.
It looks really good.
It's almost there.
They're almost here.
The phone won't stop ringing.
What the hell is this?
This is the Krona terminal,
The texture is different in two ways.
What is this?
That's great.
Thank you.
This is a very popular bag of Krona terminals,
We hope you enjoy it with us.
What's that?
It's a little bumpy, don't you think?Aren't they a little too shaky?
To all of you who love Krona terminals, please continue to enjoy them.
Yes.
Wow.
Look at this! Look at the visual!
Oh, man!
I love the visual!
Beautiful, beautiful video!
It's like foreshadowing!
You're shining just like us!
Looks delicious!
Beautiful, beautiful, beautiful!
I like beautiful women!
Thank you!
I'll go next time!
What about you, Hito-chan?
You want to do it, Hito-chan?
I'll try!
Less!
Yes! I'll do it!
I knew it!
Bon appétit!
Delicious!
Soft!
It's soft, but still has a nice crunchy texture.
Wait a minute.
Oh no. It tastes so good with tears.
It's so delicious.
I wonder what color it is.
It's firm, but it's like it's melting away.
It's right.
Delicious.
Thank you very much.
Beef tongue is delicious.
It's delicious.
This is delicious.
It's leeks, isn't it?
It's leeks, right?
It's so good.
It's leeks, right? Delicious.
Thank you, everyone.
Beef tongue is good.
I love that one.
Let's go.
It looks like it's going to cook soon.
Yes, it is.
If you put it on, it'll spread.
Please spread it out.
But if you put it on, it won't spread.
If the stick sasser does it...
Oh, yes.
Eh, seriously delicious.
But it's so bad already.
I don't know if it's okay anymore
I don't know if it's good anymore
If I flip it over one more time, I think it's ready.
Oh, wow!
Wow!
Oh my God, these sticks are so good!
It was really good.
It's really good.
He'll eat it forever.
Oh, my God.
They're gone in an instant.
It's so good.
It's almost ready.
It's been a while since we've had barbecue jarred meat.
It's good.
It's so good!
Se-no.
I love it! I love it! I love it!
I like that plan.
It's good, it's good, it's good, it's good.
It's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good.
I'm going to bake this.
Akichan, this way.
This way is great!
Okay.
I want you to grill it.
Delicious!
It's upside down.
I got it.
I want you to grill it for me.
It's delicious.
It's been a minute since I ate it, but it's still good.It's been about a minute since I ate it, but it's delicious.
Delicious.
Unmarked type.
Amazing.
It's like an outbreak practice.
It's so warm!
I see.
That's amazing.
Oh, my God.
This is the best.
This is totally different.
How can it taste so good?
How did it get so good so fast?
It's so crispy.
It's not crunchy, it's chewy.
Thank you.
I can't stop looking at it.
Looks delicious.
Oh, my God.
It's so good.
The waitress.
I made eye contact with the waitress.
What's this?
What's this in this store?
You'll be shocked.
It's delicious.
It's really good.
It's amazing.
Every week.
10 million ways every week
Ten million ways.
That's how you can come.
Hard Electrologer
Ten times
Nice to meet you all.
Look at you all.
Bye-bye.
Nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you.
Bye, bye, bye.
Yum! Yum! Yum!
Oh, my God.
Delicious.
Soft.
Yeah, it's good.
Tangy.
Good.
Delicious!
It melts!
Really!
Bon appétit!
Delicious!
This is so good!
Bread is delicious!
The meat just keeps coming!
Bon appétit!
Mmmm!
This is the menzujo roast.
Today, please eat it in about 10 seconds on one side and 5 seconds on the other side.
15 seconds?
That's great, 15 seconds.
Put down three cups.
And take a bite of the kimchi.
Three, four, five, six, eight, nine, ten.
Here we go!
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Staff, we're gonna have to send them on their way.
Are you sure?
Nonsense. Nonsense.
I'm not going to put anything on it.
Lemon. It's gone.
Soft.
I don't even have to chew it. I can swallow it.
Hey!
This San is really delicious.
What did you just eat?
It melts.
I'll get it.
It's too much.
This is amazing.
Want to try some yakiniku?
That's the first one.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
This one! This! This one! This one!
One more. One more.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
It has nothing to do with the skin.
Can you do this?
Thank you.
That one too?
What's with the skin?
Yuki!
Yuuki!
Here! This! This!
It's grilled yuki.
Please enjoy it after mixing.
Wow!
So tender!
It tastes like meat.
Wow! Delicious!
Everything is tender.
Delicious.
Thank you very much.
There's a screw.
There was a screw, wasn't there?
Akichan.
Yolk.
There's a lot of orange yolk.
Wow, it looks delicious.
Is it good?
It's delicious.
It's so beautiful.
Sorry. I'll just eat it as normal.
Wow.
Do you have a hobby?
It looks good.
Akichan hands.
Yes. Look at this, everyone.
Wow, orange.
You are too good.
It's everyone's color.
Oh, no.
Does it feel good?
How does it feel?
It's hot!
Tasty?
How is it? Is it good?
It's good.
Tasty?
Slow.
Let's pour it on.
Bon appétit.
Is it sweet?
I shared all of it.
He's sharing it shot by shot.
It's cute. It's a nice picture.
It's delicious.
Cut it.
It's delicious, Yuke.
It has a sweetness. To the meat.
It's a nice picture.
The egg has this mildness and the meat has a nice tenderness.
Eggs, the taste is still different.
It's better than the strong one.
The smile on your face.
It's hard work over here.
What is this?
Oh no.
It's like a king.
I haven't eaten for three days.
I'm so happy.
This is amazing.
They're so thin and big.
Have you ever had a head fight?
No, I haven't.
Not to this extent.
It's amazing.
They are so cute.
My eyes are a little bit watery.
Oh no.
He's so cute.
What do you think?
Oh, my king.
Thank you for your hard work.
It's beautiful.
Wow, beautiful.
My snacks are here.
Thank you for coming.
Thank you for dinner.
Egg and caramel snack.
Okay, I'll eat it.
You're too happy.
Happy face.Happy face.
Oh no.
Me too
Oh, my gosh!
Wow!
I can't believe I splurged on this.
Should I just take one bite of this?
I don't know what's wrong with me.
Oh, my God.
It's huge.
Is it?
Wow, amazing.
Wait, wait, wait. What should I do?
Can I eat it? Let's eat this.
I ate it. It's hot.
Hot, hot, hot.
I'm eating it. Hot, hot, hot.
Eat it with us.
Go ahead, Hito-chan.
How should I eat it?
Can you chew it up?
Thank you very much.
I'll eat it then.
You look so happy.
It looks so, so, so delicious.
Yum! Yum!
Delicious!
Beautiful!
She is beautiful!
Delicious!
Too hot.
She's sweating.
Great.
Cute.
Yup.
Yeah. - Yeah.
Come on, this one.
Oh, no.
Now, this is how I feel.
I'm feeling it.
After dinner, right?
Like 10:00 p.m.
I might go out for yakiniku.
Go ahead.
Great. Bon appétit.
Bon appétit.
Wow.
It's so delicious.
Here are the halami and the kalbi.
I recommend you to grill the halami well, but please enjoy the kalbi as you like.
Here is the wild layer.
My rarest part is made into a rice ball.
Rare part.
Tender.
The texture when you bite it is too soft.
Tollo.
Still different from other meats.
It's amazing.
Amazing.
It's so soft.
Inside and out.
What is this? Harami?
Harami?
It's amazing.
If you come here, you should eat this on the way.
Sesame tongue.
I recommend it.
It's so delicious.
Thank you for the food.
Let's have a hoo-hoo!
Next, next, next.
There you go.
Wipe me down.
That's not good.
What was the best part?
Oh, no.
It's so good, everyone forgets.
I still like the bread.
It was a shock, wasn't it? One bite.
That's because it came first.
I thought it would be hard,
It's really soft,
It was a nice shock.
Wasn't that tasty too? Onsen egg.
It was delicious!
Kuroda-yaki?
Kuroda Special.
Oh, no!Oh, no.
Oh, my God.
Wow.
Yay!
I love it! I love it! I love it!
He's so cute!
Adorable.
So sweet.
Look at them.
Look at this!
Yay!
Oh, my gosh! And the newest Arasha!
Oh, my God!
Yay!
Thank you!
So, once again, thank you all for watching 10 million times!
So, Yukimi-kun, Kuroda-san and I had the pleasure of eating your reward this time!
Thanks to all of you!
Thanks to all of you who watched the skiing, I was able to lift up a very happy mood!
Thank you so much!
And the cake!
It's amazing!
Shall we eat it now?
We will continue to do our best so that many people can see and know us, so please continue to support us!
Please keep supporting us!
Thank you very much, Yukimi!
Thank you for the food!
I was so happy!
Thank you so much!
The town after the rain, the waves are shimmering
My heart is like a sunny day, playing the rainbow piano with the sound of puddles.
I don't know why, but when I smile, it's as if the world is shining.
I can turn my umbrella around and take it easy 'Cause I wouldn't be able to walk otherwise
# Somewhere someone's crying # Somewhere I'll get wet again and not get cold #
# I'm sure somewhere someone's crying # I just want to share a little bit of me with them #
I still don't know the scenery in front of me.
Good-bye and goodbye. Thank you for yesterday. After the rain, the cityscape turned color.
And on the canvas of my broken heart, a piece of the future will be painted to guide me.
I can say it now.
Whenever you're lost, remember the reason for your tears
And when it's raining, I'll smile
Come on, let's go wherever you want
Good bye, good bye, to the me of yesterday
After the rain, the streets are shimmering
My heart is like a sunny sky, rainbow pools and sounds
I play the rainbow piano
Good bye Good bye to me yesterday
After the rain, the streets are shimmering
My heart is like a rainbow, crossing the clouds of tears
I'm gonna wear a rainbow dress
Please subscribe to our channel!